One Two Three Four
I couldn't wait for you to
come and clear the cupboard
But now you're gone and leaving nothing but a  sign
Another evening I'll be sitting reading in between your lines
Because I miss you all the time
So, get away
Another way to feel what you didn't want yourself to know
And let yourself go
You know you didn't lose your self-control
Let's start at the rainbow
Turn away
Another way to be where you didn't want yourself to go
And let yourself go
Is that a compromise?
So, what do you wanna do, what's your point of view?
There's a party, screw it, do you wanna go?
A handshake with you, what's your point of view?
I'm on top of you, I don't wanna go
'Cause I really wanna stay at your house
And I hope it all works out
But you know how much you broke me apart
I'm done with you, I'm ignoring you
I don't wanna know
[ Music ]
And I'm awarе that you were lying in the gutter
'Cause I did everything to be there by your side-ide
So when you tell me I'm the reason, I just can't believe the lies
And why do I still wanna call you
So, what do you wanna do, what's your point of view?
There's a party, screw it, do you wanna go?
A handshake with you, what's your point of view?
I'm on top of you, I don't wanna go
'Cause I really wanna stay at your house
And I hope it all works out
But you know how much you broke me apart
I'm done with you, I'm ignoring you
I don't wanna know
[Music]
I don't know why I'm no one
So, get away
Another way to feel what you didn't want yourself to know
And let yourself go
You know you didn't lose your self-control
Let's start at the rainbow
Turn away
Another way to be where you didn't want yourself to go
And let yourself go
Is that a compromise?
So what do you wanna do, what's your point of view?
There's a party, screw it, do you wanna go?
A handshake with you, what's your point of view?
I'm on top of you, I don't wanna go
'Cause I really wanna stay at your house
And I hope it all works out
But you know how much you broke me apart
I'm done with you, I'm ignoring you
I don't wanna know
[ Thanks for watching ]